So here we have the basic app running
现在展示的是在 iOS 和 Android 上的
from create React Native app on iOS as well as Android.
Create React Native 应用上运行的基本应用
And what I want to show you in this video is how to
我在本视频中要演示的是
open up the developer menus and both of these,
如何在这两个应用中打开开发者菜单
and also how to debug an application,
以及如何调试应用
so when the time comes you can easily do that.
在必要时使你能够轻松地调试代码
So, if you're using the iOS simulator over here,
如果你在使用 iOS 模拟器
go ahead and select it and then hit command D and that will open up this menu right here.
选择它 按下 Command+D 后会打开此菜单
You'll notice that we have a few options.
你会注意到几个选项
We can refresh, we can copy link,
我们可以刷新 复制链接
we can disable live view, all of these things.
停用实时视图 等等
But what I'm interested in right now is this one right here called Debug Remote JS.
但是我要介绍的是这个 Debug Remote JS
If you go ahead and select that,
选择该选项后
what's going to happen is React Native is going to open up another window.
React Native 将打开另一个窗口
So now in this window,
在此窗口中
if we open up the console just as we're used to,
如果和之前一样打开控制台
you'll see some stuff going on here.
将看到一些代码
Right. We have some warnings.
有一些警告
And now if I wanted to put a debugger in my apple,
如果我想在应用中添加调试器
say we want to debug whenever this component mounts.
假设每当该组件加载时 我们希望能调试下
All we need to do, just like we're used to,
我们只需和之前一样
is we will throw in a debugger.
添加调试器
So here I would say, cancel that log,
在这里输出控制台日志“before”
let's say before, and then we will constitute a log after.
然后输出日志“after”
So I hit save,
点击保存
that goes and refreshes my app because the live reload is on.
这样就会刷新应用 因为我开启了实时重新加载功能
And then you'll notice, if we go back over to our console,
然后你会发现 如果回到控制台
we are now in the console just as we are on the web.
我们位于控制台中 就像位于网页上
And so what I can do here is you'll see that we got before,
我们可以看到这个 before,
then we go ahead and step through this again just like we're on the web.
然后就像在网页上一页 转到下面
We get after, everything is the same.
获得 after 一切都一样
So what's great about react native is the same development experience you're used to
React Native 的好处是在网页上的开发体验
on the web is the exact same with react native because we can log to the console,
在 React Native 中完全一样 因为我们可以向控制台输出日志
we can throw in a debugger.
可以插入调试器
Everything is so familiar.
一切都很熟悉
And so to get the developer menu on android instead
在 Android 上 要打开开发者菜单
of hitting command D like we did in iOS on android,
按下 Command+D
you hit command M and we get the same option right here.
而不是 Command+M 然后获得这些选项
But I want to go back to iOS real quick.
我再次回到 iOS 应用
And I want to select one more option.
我想再选择一个选项
You'll notice here that we have Toggle Element Inspector and this can be native.
这里有个 Toggle Element Inspector
This is like kind of selecting elements on the web or I can click on any of
这就像在网页上选择元素一样
these and I can get any style to apply to it as well as any padding margin.
我可以点击任何一个元素并获得应用到其上的样式和任何内外间距
Basically the box model inspector that we have on the web,
对于网页上的 Box Model Inspector
we can have this with react native and say,
我们在 React Native 中也有相应的选项
I wanted to click on one of these without inspecting it.
假设我想点击其中一个元素 并且不检测它
All we have to do is select this box right
我只需选择这个方框
here and then now when we click, it won't inspect.
现在点击的话 不会检测了
So we can toggle this on and off and to remove it again,
我们可以打开或关闭此选项 要取消它
all we do is hit command D and then click on toggle element inspector.
只需按下 Command+D 然后点击 Toggle Element Inspector
So there's a bunch of stuff you can do here with the developer options here.
开发者选项中有很多可以选择的内容
The biggest ones you'll need are refreshing,
最重要的功能是刷新
toggle element inspector as well as starting and stopping the remote debugger.
Toggle Element Inspector 以及启动和停止远程调试器